export default {
  id: 'addition-c',
  type: 'interview',
  attributes: {
    operator: '+',
    questions: [
      {
        prompt: '1 + 1',
        answer: 2,
        column: 1
      },
      {
        prompt: '5 + 1',
        answer: 6,
        column: 1
      },
      {
        prompt: '3 + 1',
        answer: 4,
        column: 1
      },
      {
        prompt: '8 + 1',
        answer: 9,
        column: 1
      },
      {
        prompt: '2 + 2',
        answer: 4,
        column: 1
      },
      {
        prompt: '7 + 1',
        answer: 8,
        column: 1
      },
      {
        prompt: '6 + 1',
        answer: 7,
        column: 1
      },
      {
        prompt: '2 + 1',
        answer: 3,
        column: 1
      },
      {
        prompt: '4 + 1',
        answer: 5,
        column: 1
      },
      {
        prompt: '9 + 1',
        answer: 10,
        column: 1
      },
      {
        prompt: '5 + 5',
        answer: 10,
        column: 2
      },
      {
        prompt: '1 + 2',
        answer: 3,
        column: 2
      },
      {
        prompt: '1 + 4',
        answer: 5,
        column: 2
      },
      {
        prompt: '1 + 3',
        answer: 4,
        column: 2
      },
      {
        prompt: '1 + 7',
        answer: 8,
        column: 2
      },
      {
        prompt: '1 + 5',
        answer: 6,
        column: 2
      },
      {
        prompt: '3 + 3',
        answer: 6,
        column: 2
      },
      {
        prompt: '1 + 8',
        answer: 9,
        column: 2
      },
      {
        prompt: '1 + 6',
        answer: 7,
        column: 2
      },
      {
        prompt: '4 + 4',
        answer: 8,
        column: 2
      },
      {
        prompt: '3 + 2',
        answer: 5,
        column: 3
      },
      {
        prompt: '4 + 0',
        answer: 4,
        column: 3
      },
      {
        prompt: '5 + 2',
        answer: 7,
        column: 3
      },
      {
        prompt: '2 + 3',
        answer: 5,
        column: 3
      },
      {
        prompt: '7 + 2',
        answer: 9,
        column: 3
      },
      {
        prompt: '0 + 5',
        answer: 5,
        column: 3
      },
      {
        prompt: '4 + 2',
        answer: 6,
        column: 3
      },
      {
        prompt: '6 + 2',
        answer: 8,
        column: 3
      },
      {
        prompt: '8 + 2',
        answer: 10,
        column: 3
      },
      {
        prompt: '2 + 5',
        answer: 7,
        column: 3
      },
      {
        prompt: '5 + 3',
        answer: 8,
        column: 4
      },
      {
        prompt: '2 + 8',
        answer: 10,
        column: 4
      },
      {
        prompt: '3 + 4',
        answer: 7,
        column: 4
      },
      {
        prompt: '0 + 9',
        answer: 9,
        column: 4
      },
      {
        prompt: '6 + 3',
        answer: 9,
        column: 4
      },
      {
        prompt: '4 + 3',
        answer: 7,
        column: 4
      },
      {
        prompt: '5 + 4',
        answer: 9,
        column: 4
      },
      {
        prompt: '3 + 6',
        answer: 9,
        column: 4
      },
      {
        prompt: '6 + 0',
        answer: 6,
        column: 4
      },
      {
        prompt: '4 + 5',
        answer: 9,
        column: 4
      },
      {
        prompt: '3 + 5',
        answer: 8,
        column: 5
      },
      {
        prompt: '7 + 3',
        answer: 10,
        column: 5
      },
      {
        prompt: '2 + 6',
        answer: 8,
        column: 5
      },
      {
        prompt: '2 + 4',
        answer: 6,
        column: 5
      },
      {
        prompt: '6 + 4',
        answer: 10,
        column: 5
      },
      {
        prompt: '2 + 7',
        answer: 9,
        column: 5
      },
      {
        prompt: '3 + 7',
        answer: 10,
        column: 5
      },
      {
        prompt: '1 + 9',
        answer: 10,
        column: 5
      },
      {
        prompt: '4 + 6',
        answer: 10,
        column: 5
      },
      {
        prompt: '10 + 0',
        answer: 10,
        column: 5
      }
    ]
  }
};